stacktips.com 2018-07-25

# Privacy Policy – StackTips

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

We consider our readers privacy seriously! We are committed to protect the privacy and accuracy of confidential information to the extent possible. This document outlines our privacy policy statement to and about our information gathering and dissemination practices.

StackTips readers are free to visit, comment, test and download code snippets, examples, docs, etc. without any user registration. Stacktips may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. This privacy document applies only to stacktips.com.

## Personal Information

Although there are many applications and websites that collect information and other statistics about their users, Stacktips **DO NOT** collect any personal information or use cookies about you when you visit this website.

If you contact us via this website, you might provide your name and email address. Such informations are solely used for the purpose of replying to your enquiry. Any of your details are not used for any other reason and is not passed to anyone else without your consent.

IP addresses are logged for aggregate statistics and diagnosis. We use third party sites for statistics and analysis purpose. We have implemented and use display advertising through re-marketing with Google analytics.

## Cookies

Cookies are small files placed on your computer which can log certain information about your visit. For instance, we use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
We use cookies to:

  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * To understand your content of your interest to serve you with better quality content.

### Google

We use third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. The information is stored by Google is adhered to Google’s privacy policy.

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

## Contact

This privacy statement was last revised on 15th June 2016 We may change this privacy statement at any time and for any reason. If you have questions or comments about this privacy statement, please write to support[at]stacktips.com.
